postso.com 2016-04-08

# Privacy Policy - - Posts - Posting and scheduling to Instagram, Pinterest, Facebook, Twitter, VK.com

Our privacy policy explains how information is collected, used and disclosed by Posts with respect to your access and use of Posts’s services. 

### What information do we collect?

We collect certain information you provide to us when using Posts, such as when you create an account and profile, send us an email or post information or other content to Posts We collect certain personal information, like your name, picture, email address and phone number, as well as certain non-identifying information, like your gender, birthday and zip code. We will also collect the contact information of your friends, if you choose to connect your contacts and address book information with Posts and your login credentials to your social network accounts, if you choose to connect those accounts with your Posts account.

We also automatically collect certain information when you use Posts, such as your location/GPS coordinates (if you enable this feature), a device identifier (but not the UDID), MAC address, wireless service provider, Internet Protocol (IP) address, operating system, the browser type, the address of a referring site and your activity on Posts. You can enable or disable location services when you use Posts at anytime, through your browser settings. This information is not treated as personal information unless we combine it with or link it to any of the personally identifiable information mentioned above.

We may also automatically collect certain information through the use of “cookies”. These are small files that your browser places on your computer. We may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with our services, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on our services, and to improve our services. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit.

### How do we use the information we collect?

We use the information collected through Posts for the purposes described below:

  * to provide our services or information you request, and to process and complete any transactions; 
  * to respond to your emails, submissions, questions, comments, requests, and complaints and provide customer service; 
  * to monitor and analyze usage and trends, and to personalize and improve Posts and your experiences when you use Posts, such as providing content or features that match your profile or interests (including ads), and to increase the functionality and user friendliness of our services; 
  * to send you confirmations, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages and otherwise facilitate your use of, and our administration and operation of, our services; 
  * to allow you to add your location to your posts; 
  * for any other purpose for which the information was collected. 

### What information do we share with third parties?

We will not share the personal information we have collected from you, except as described below:

  * with certain social networking services, if you allow such sharing through our services;
  * with service providers who are working with us in connection with the operation of our site or our services (these service providers have access to your personal information only to perform services on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose it or use it for any other purposes);
  * we may share aggregated information and non-identifiable information with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling and other similar purposes;
  * when you give us your consent to do so, including if we notify you that the information you provide will be shared in a particular manner and you provide such information;
  * when we believe in good faith that we are lawfully authorized or required to do so or that doing so is reasonably necessary or appropriate to comply with the law or legal processes or respond to lawful requests or legal authorities, including responding to lawful subpoenas, warrants or court orders;
  * to enforce or apply our privacy policy, our terms of use or our other policies or agreements; and in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition, or in any other situation where personal information may be disclosed or transferred as one of our business assets.

We are not responsible for the actions of service providers or other third parties, nor are we responsible for any additional information you provide directly to any third parties. 

### Security

We are very concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information. We implement a variety of administrative, physical and electronic security measures to to protect your information from unauthorized access.

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. And users can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Links to Other Websites

Posts contains links to other websites. The fact that we link to a website is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personally identifiable information from you. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personally identifiable information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.

### Our policy toward children

Our service is not directed to children under 13 and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we learn that we have collected personal information of a child under 13, we will take steps to delete such information from our files as soon as possible.

### Use of Web Analytic Services

The following web analytic services are used to improve the user experience of our Website.

  * We use Google Analytics, a service for the marketing analysis of this website, of Google Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses codes consisting of text and numbers, which will be stored on your computer and which allow for an analysis of the use of the Websites ("Cookies"). The information generated by the Cookie about your use of the Websites (including your IP address) will be transferred to and stored by a Google Server. Google will use this information, to evaluate your use of the website, to prepare reports about the website activities for the website operators and to provide further services connected to the use of websites and the use of the Internet. Google may transfer this information to third parties, if legally obliged to do so or if third parties process these data on behalf of Google. In no case, Google will connect your IP address with other data from Google. Please note that our Websites uses Google Analytics with the extension '_anonymizelp()' and consequently IP addresses are only used in shortened form in order to prevent direct personal references. 
  * We use Mixpanel, an advanced analytics service provided by Mixpanel, Inc. ("Mixpanel") that helps improve web and mobile applications by tracking how users interact and engage. Usage information and Personal Data is stored by Mixpanel and is subject to their privacy policy. You can view their privacy policy at https://mixpanel.com/privacy. 
  * We use Intercom, a third party analytics service provided by Intercom, Inc. ("Intercom") to help understand your use of our services and to communicate with you by sending you service-related notifications in the Posts interface. Posts uses Intercom to collect data for analytics purposes when you use our services. Intercom analyzes your use of our website and/or service and our relationship with you, so that we can improve our services. For more information on the privacy practices of Intercom, please check http://docs.intercom.io/privacy. Intercom’s services are governed by Intercom’s terms of use, which can be found at http://docs.intercom.io/terms.

### Changes to this Policy

Any information that is collected is subject to the privacy policy in effect at the time such information is collected. We may, however, modify and revise our privacy policy from time-to-time. If we make any material changes to this policy, we will notify you of such changes by posting them on Path or by sending you an email or other notification, and we will indicate when such changes will become effective. By continuing to access or use Posts after those changes become effective, you are agreeing to be bound by the revised policy.

### Questions?

Please [contact us](mailto:feedback@posts.so) if you have any questions about our privacy policy.

Effective: November 7, 2013
